[{"answer": "Well, it tells me that the special prosecutor is not going to use a copout.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "What does that tell you as a prominent lawyer?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's bad news for Zimmerman.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "If you were representing him, how would you be feeling tonight?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Well, if the evidence shows that he was acting in self-defense and that his fear was reasonable, then yes, under the law that would be an absolute defense.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "If that is proven to be the case, if those facts are proved by evidence, will he get off under \"Stand Your Ground,\" do you believe?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, we don't know yet.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Or is this very likely now to go to a trial where a jury will decide?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Can I add to this?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, it's much more difficult if he is the aggressor.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "If those signs of evidence were actually caused as a result of George Zimmerman starting the altercation -- I mean if for argument's sake he approached Trayvon Martin and began pushing him around, where does that leave him defense under \"Stand Your Ground\"?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "You have -- you put your finger right on it.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "We don't know much about Trayvon Martin in terms of his condition, do we?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Well, you know, he doesn't have, you know, photographs or videos of a child to sell like Casey Anthony did to raise money for her defense.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "What was your take on it?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I would say he's making a big mistake.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "We go to Alan first for your reaction?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Let me be even shorter.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Yes or no to an arrest within seven days?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Neighborhood watch, right?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "You know, if you take the right to bear arms, it doesn't mean the right to have a tank in your back garden, does it?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Have a bigger lottery.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What can it physically, realistically do to change this?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "He's less threatening than a Santorum, isn't he?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "The single thing is that -- the thing I saw today that we're not training --", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Very quickly, what is the single thing that's made you the most furious since I last saw you?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I don't know how.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "How can that be happening?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I think whoever wins in November should put you in there just to foam at them.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Then they are putting their two groups -- I can't remember the name.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "How can you not doing more in work training at this time?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Well, he's done nothing to me.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "What's he done to you?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "The Jewish is either -- bringing something up or, you know, a belch, one or the other.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "What is the Jewish version of the Tebow?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "The engine's beginning to run again?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Literally, I've never seen that happen before.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Did I really?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "I think number two much more than number one.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "So has Mark Zuckerberg done this because he sees this as a brilliant new tool to enhance Facebook or to crush a potential opponent by buying them out of the market?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "We saw that in 2000.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Could it be a boom that leads to a quick bubble burst?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Well, but I take it -- I take it one of the things -- their claim to fame is that -- yes, is that photographers who think they're good can massage and --", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "It is a slightly mad world, isn't it?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I think Path has a shot.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "What's the next big sale going to be?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "The word on the street is they're raising Around a 250 million valuation.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "What was it presumed to be worth yesterday and what will it be worth tomorrow, based on Instagram?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you look at investigative reporting on television, he was the pioneer in that.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "What will his legacy be, do you think?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "I'm fine.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "Simon Johnson, how are you?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "I love this book title, \"White House Burning,\" because further investigation revealed it's reference to a War of 1812, when war hawks they taxes, didn't fund the military, got rid of the Central Bank.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Well, the Founding Fathers, first of all, would have been stunned to see the U.S. as the number one world economic and political power.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "What would the Founding Fathers have made of America being 15.6 trillion dollars in debt?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "I have problems with both.", "docId": "120409pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Come on, just cut to the quick, Romney or Obama, who has -- you have to keep this quite brief -- the best solution, do you think, if it's those two head to head in November, to the economic woes America is facing?", "qSentId": 684}]